http://www.smothers.com/store/site/privacy

Privacy Policy
We at Smothers Auto Parts know that you care how information about you is used and shared. As part of its commitment to customer service, Smothers Auto Parts strives to make you feel safe and comfortable doing business with us. Here are some guidelines Smothers Auto Parts follows to keep your personal information private. Smothers Auto Parts reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion without notice.
Information Collection
Smothers Auto Parts may collect certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to name, address, telephone number, and email address. Smothers Auto Parts may also collect your credit card information and billing address when you provide Smothers Auto Parts with such information.
The Web Site may use third party products and services to gather anonymous traffic statistics using cookies and web beacons. A cookie is a small piece of information stored with your browser that helps web sites and multiple servers recognize you. Smothers Auto Parts and its third party service providers may also use pixels, or transparent GIF files, for web site management and user tracking.
Smothers Auto Parts transmits non-personally identifiable user information about visitors to the servers of reputable third parties for the purpose of targeting its internet banner advertisements on other sites.
Information Use
Smothers Auto Parts may share personal customer information provided to Smothers Auto Parts with third parties who provide services and products to Smothers Auto Parts. Examples of ways in which your information may be used include, but are not limited to, the following:
- Order fulfillment
- Marketing activities including direct mail, e-mail, database cleaning and maintenance, and analysis
- Customer experience enhancements
- Warranty management
Smothers Auto Parts is not in the business of selling its customers' personal information to others. Smothers Auto Parts does not sell, rent or trade its customers' personal information to third parties.
Smothers Auto Parts also collects, stores, and uses aggregate data that do not contain personally identifiable information, such as demographics or statistical information. This aggregate data may be shared with and used by third parties to help Smothers Auto Parts and its suppliers better understand and serve our customers.
Your Choices
While Smothers Auto Parts encourages you to take advantage of the personalized services on our website, you can use most of Smothers Auto Parts's online services without registering your information with Smothers Auto Parts. You can change your information at any time by editing your profile. If you are registered on Smothers Auto Parts.com.
Although Smothers Auto Parts may link to other web sites, Smothers Auto Parts is not responsible for and does not control the security or privacy when you visit those sites. Smothers Auto Parts encourages you to visit the privacy notices governing those sites.
Updates to this Privacy Policy
From time to time, Smothers Auto Parts may modify this Privacy Policy. Smothers Auto Parts will notify you of any material changes to its Privacy Policy by posting those changes on this page and updating the Privacy Policy modification date above. Smothers Auto Parts encourages you periodically to check back to this page for any updates.
How to Contact Us
If you have questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this site, please contact Smothers Auto Parts by clicking here.
Copyright © 2020 Smothers Auto Parts & Performance Accessories
Powered By SiteAlive Inc.
